{
    "questions": {
        "categories": [
            {
                "category": 1,
                "name": "Music",
                "questions":
                [
                    {
                        "points": 200,
                        "Question": "Who was a member of One Direction?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Nial Horan",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Justin Bieber",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Shawn Mendes"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 400,
                        "Question": "Who has won the most Grammys in history?",
                        "correctAnswer": "George Solti",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Beyonce",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Stevie Wonder"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 600,
                        "Question": "Who is the highest grossing musician of all time?",
                        "correctAnswer": "The Beatles",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Elvis Presley",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Michael Jackson"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 800,
                        "Question": "What is the most streamed song on Spotify?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Shape of You - Ed Sheeran",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Radioactive - Imagine Dragons",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "One Dance - Drake"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 1000,
                        "Question": "What was the best selling album of 2012?",
                        "correctAnswer": "21 - Adele",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Recovery - Eminem",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Midnight Memories - One Direction"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": 2,
                "name": "Fast Food",
                "questions":
                [
                    {
                        "points": 200,
                        "Question": "What fast food chain is known for selling the 4 for $4?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Wendy's",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Burger King",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Arbys"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 400,
                        "Question": "What drink does McDonald's NOT sell?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Diet Pepsi",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Dr. Pepper",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Sprite"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 600,
                        "Question": "What fast food chain has the most locations in the USA?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Subway",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "McDonald's",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Taco Bell"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 800,
                        "Question": "What was Panera Bread's original Name?",
                        "correctAnswer": "St. Louis Bread Company",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Brad's Bread and Bruch",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Bravo's Bakery"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 1000,
                        "Question": "When did Burger King introduce The Whopper?",
                        "correctAnswer": "1957",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "1968",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "1951"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": 3,
                "name": "Sitcoms",
                "questions":
                [
                    {
                        "points": 200,
                        "Question": "What sitcom did Mary Kate and Ashley Olson start in?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Full House",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Family Matters",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Sister Sister"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 400,
                        "Question": "What sitcom has the character of Leslie Knope?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Parks and Recreation",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "The Office",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Arrest Development"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 600,
                        "Question": "What was the longest running sitcom of all time?",
                        "correctAnswer": "It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Friends",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Married ... With Children"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 800,
                        "Question": "On Seinfeld, who was Jerry's neighbor?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Kramer",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Elaine",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "George"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 1000,
                        "Question": "On Friends, how many times did Ross get married?",
                        "correctAnswer": "3",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "4",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "0"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": 4,
                "name": "Cartoons",
                "questions":
                [
                    {
                        "points": 200,
                        "Question": "Which cartoon ran on Disney Channel?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Phineas and Ferb",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "CatDog",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Scooby-Doo"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 400,
                        "Question": "Where does Spongebob work?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Krusty Crab",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Chum Bucket",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Salty Spitoon"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 600,
                        "Question": "What is a not a color of one of the Powerpuff Girls?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Yellow",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Pink",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Green"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 800,
                        "Question": "What fictional city does Hey Arnold! take place in?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Hillwood",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Sky City",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Lakeview Park"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 1000,
                        "Question": "In the Fairly Odd Parents, who is Timmy's babysitter?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Vicky",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Trudy",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Mark"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": 5,
                "name": "Cars",
                "questions":
                [
                    {
                        "points": 200,
                        "Question": "Which vehicle is produced by Toyota?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Avalon",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Accord",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Passat"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 400,
                        "Question": "What car is no longer manufactored?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Volkswagen Beetle ",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Ford Bronco",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Honda Civic"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 600,
                        "Question": "What car brand stopped producing vehicles in 2009?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Pontiac",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Saturn",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Plymouth"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 800,
                        "Question": "What is the best selling sedan of all time?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Corolla",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Camry",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Focus"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 1000,
                        "Question": "What car did Rory Gilmore have in Gilmore Girls?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Prius",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Cherokee",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "XC60"
                    }
                ]
            },
            {
                "category": 6,
                "name": "Cities",
                "questions":
                [
                    {
                        "points": 200,
                        "Question": "What is the largest city is the USA?",
                        "correctAnswer": "New York City",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Los Angeles",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Chicago"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 400,
                        "Question": "What is the largest city in Texas?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Houston",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Dallas",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Austin"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 600,
                        "Question": "What is the largest city in Wisconsin?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Milwaukee",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Madison",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Green Bay"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 800,
                        "Question": "What is the smallest city in the USA?",
                        "correctAnswer": "River Forest, IN",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Buffalo, SD",
                        "wrongAnswer2": "Apple, MN"
                    },
                    {
                        "points": 1000,
                        "Question": "What city does the Sock Monkey originate in?",
                        "correctAnswer": "Rockford, IL",
                        "wrongAnswer1": "Denver, CO",
                        "wrongAnswer2": " Aurora, IL"
                    }
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
}